The top is also miso paste, disguised as dried plums.
It is miso. It's delicious, isn't it?
Why do they look like someone spilled it like that?
Why don't you put a little more on top?
It's not that cut and dried, is it?
Then sue me.
Sue. The bento is too monotonous.
Well then.
May I begin?
Please do.
Whoa!
Now it's complete.
You know, you have stronger eyes than you think.
You scared the shit out of me.
No, no, no, thank you.
Thank you very much for joining us today.
It's been a week since I've seen you... well, you know, for a moment there, you're all... you're all smiling, but you've been like that the whole time.
Bragg, you've been behind the scenes.
It's not like that, folks.
He's got a great voice. He's an ace.
So, we're going to start off this week with a little blessing and a blessing.
So here we are, the weekend of the Devil in the House, as you might expect.
I'm sure everyone's had a few drinks today... but it's Friday.
I wonder if they're still drinking? You can watch the show while you drink.
I wonder where they are...
I'm not sure where everyone is, but I'm sure they're eating delicious food.
It's rare... rare... that photo of the persimmon... rare...
A lot of persimmons. Food leaves a lasting impression, doesn't it?
I had a bit of a row with him earlier about the food in his lunch box.
The Kin number bento is good, it's good, it's good.
It's good. It's a Kin number, but can't we have just one more minute?
By the way, it's March 8th, the day of the three bowls.
That's why...
You probably know that the honey is made by Mitsubachi.
There are two kinds of honey.
Yes, two kinds. Is that so surprising?
No, no, no, I've never heard of them.
Are you saying they're working pots or not?
Not at all. Can I ask you to be quiet for a minute?
Can I ask you to shut up for a second?
What do you think it is?
You see the different colors of the honey?
I'm just wondering if there's a darker one and a lighter one.
Doesn't that make a difference?
That's what makes the difference.
By the way, there are two types, the Japanese three-bowl honeybee and the Western three-bowl honeybee.
There are two types: the Japanese Mitsubachi and the Western Mitsubachi, which were originally from Japan and imported from overseas.
By the way, the Western Mitsubachi imported from overseas makes a lot of honey.
Wow, they work hard!
The honey we eat is mostly Western honey, but the Japanese honey is actually very rich and different.
But the Japanese honey is actually very rich and different.
Today is the day of the three bowls, so I'd like to invite you to the three bowls car.
A three-tooth bowl wheel? It's just a coincidence, but it's amazing.
Everyone has been sending me lots of pictures, but this one is very timely.
Atsushi Bunkyo-ku, Tokyo Thank you very much.
He's a regular, but I'm sure he knows how the show is going to go.
That's why the name "flower" is blooming.
I'm not exaggerating when I say that I love, love, love bugs, and they were hard at work.
I'd like to send you a picture of a cute little bug. How did you manage to get such a close shot of this cute little guy? That's amazing.
What kind of camera are you using? With a cell phone?
No, thank you. I mean, I guess you could take pictures with a cell phone, but they move so much.
It's fast, isn't it? He's so cute.
What's going on? Are you okay? You made it. You're okay, 3-Star.
Are you sure? Are you okay? I'm fine from this distance.
Do you want me to take a good look? Yes, she's cute.
She's got a kind of a façade, like a madam.
She seems to have money. Yes, she does.
And she's a three-star. And she's got a quote.
This is a quote....
I don't know exactly who said it, but there are a lot of gals here.
Choroman sent me a quote from one of them.
May I? It's impossible to live without regret.
What will you do after you regret it?
That's what I'm talking about, gal mind.
You're right.
Thank you very much.
And, what else should we do? We've got lots of great photos of floats, floats, mountains...
I've got a lot of good photos here... floats, floats, mountains...
It's in the western part of Kanagawa... but it's so close to the Tanzawa Mountains.
What's wrong? What's Tanzawa?
A person's name? Tanzawa is...
The whole mountain range in Kanagawa. Are you on it?
Don't ever say that. It's not true.
By the way, you took the photo from his hometown.
The day after it snowed in Kanagawa Prefecture, I took this picture of Tanzawa, which is called the roof of Kanagawa.
The snow-covered mountains looked like an Alpine scene.
So, let's have a look at the float first.
This is definitely only in Sumisawa.
People say they'll be sad.
What's strange is that the mountains of Sumizawa are covered with snow, but the mountains in front are not covered with snow at all.
It seems this is the case every year, the mountains of Sumizawa catch all the snowy clouds and this side of the mountain doesn't get much snow.
It's so beautiful, it's like I wrote it on my hand.
It's nice to see a float once in a while. I love floats. I love mountains.
I love mountains, especially this ridge on this mountain that runs through this part of the mountain.
I love high school.
"Both lines"? Both lines? I'm sure there are many who say "both lines.
It's also, you know, in the evening, it's a little orange...
You can go as many times as you want.
If you have any good pictures of the two train lines, please send them to me.
Please send us pictures of your floats.
Let's see...
I'm the burger truck. A burger truck? A burger truck? You have such a thing?
Yes, a burger truck. They have everything. It's called a bar cart.
And by the way, the one in your grandma's picture is a bar cart too.
Is this one more expensive? That's my grandma.
By the way, Makuhaku seems to love burgers... and has been to our restaurant in Machida before.
I recommend the great overmaster, the energetic and cute Ebichu-chan, Burger King Sama-pon-san.
Thank you very much for your continued support to our staff, and good evening, this is Makuhmaku, and I would like to report that we had a delicious burger at Burger King.
I'm here to report that I had a delicious burger on the "Sotetsu Line" which goes from Yokohama to Ebiner and back.
There's a station called "Emperor's Palace", and it's pretty close to the Emperor's Palace.
There is a restaurant called "Daian Grill" which serves hamburgers and such, and it's amazing!
Can I get a hamburger out of the blue? Suddenly? The hamburger is amazing!
Look at this picture.
May I? It's a green curry soup.
I guess they want you to dip it in this.
I've never seen this type of curry before.
I've never seen this type of food before. And there seems to be some kind of cheese involved.
It's absolutely delicious! I can't get enough of it!
Subie-san is amazing when it comes to food photos!
Subie, your eyes are more powerful than you think. It's as if you're really going to get eaten.
But we talked a lot about burgers, and you do have strong eyes.
I saw Subie in Hoshino's play before, and when I went to see her...
When I went to see her in Hoshino's play, you know, she was really good.
I was so surprised, I thought he had a natural talent for acting.
I still remember that when I met him, he always had this kind of look in his eyes.
He had such strong eyes.
Only Subie or Golgo 13 have that kind of power in their eyes.
It's like, "Wow!
By the way, they serve homemade lemonade!
Wow, it's delicious!
Isn't this the fried chicken thing that Subie loves?
Looks so delicious!
The way they're dressed is so stylish! It's a little bit American style!
I'll have to make a little trip to the Emperor's Castle... maybe...
It's so close... so close... so close...
It's so close... so close... so close... so close...
I'm sure you'll understand if we don't go to this corner.
What's that? That's it!
Imagine the creature!
It's so light today.
Yes, that's why.
Yes...
There are two.
I have two.
A or B?
Excuse me.
A and B.
When I'm asked to choose between A and B, I usually choose A, so I'll choose B.
I see.
What? I'll just connect it to B. I see. B. Yes, I understand.
Setsuko from Osaka, Mr. Kampo, it's a man. If he's from Osaka, maybe he's watching the live broadcast.
Thank you, Mr. Kampo. Look at him with your eyes.
I'm sorry, I feel like I'm being offended. What's the creature's name?
Oban.
Oban? A creature called "Oban", which, by the way, is a very major creature.
It's a creature that you may have seen before.
Oban.
I know it's a familiar creature... I don't know much about it from the name "Oban"...
I know this creature, of course, but I wonder what makes it an "oban." I don't think there's much of a link between the name and the creature, though.
I don't think it's linked to the name.
It's called "Oban Blue My," isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
Yes, Oban.
I wonder what it is...
Well, but...
All kinds of creatures, really.
No, I actually knew this creature, by the way.
just in time
I thought it was something like that.
I knew it.
I saw it yesterday, too.
You saw it yesterday? Wait a minute.
That's what I was thinking.
Are you sure?
Then it's definitely not like that.
The big one.
What's this?
But it's totally fine if you write it as "big number.
Maybe I'm right.
It's not a section where you have to try to get the right answer, but it would be great if you got it right, wouldn't it?
Let's see how good your eyes are.
It's a big number, that's for sure.
If you say so, then I've often received dumpling-skin Ohashi... curlers...
I see... so there's a possibility that somehow we're going to get caught in the middle of all this.
I'm sure it's a celebration, so it's probably just a childhood gift, and when it grows up it'll be wrapped up, and then it could end up being burned.
I wonder if it's edible... it would be a miserable creature... yes, yes, yes, yes... so, please, teacher... the big number... here's a loaf of bread.
I'm not sure what you're talking about, but I've been watching an anime called "Dungeon Foods" lately.
I've been watching an anime called "Dungeon Meal" and it's about a coin worm that appears in the "Dungeon Meal" series...
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes...
I think it's a cicada...
I don't know... it's not like that...
You know... there's a "big guard"... in the old days... like a "small guard"...
Like one or two cars...
I believe they are cicadas similar to those.
Cicadas are the ones that mingle in the summer.
It's a far cry from what I'm used to.
Are these cicadas? Am I seeing things? Is it a cicada at all?
Is it a cicada at all? I think I know what you mean.
These are wings.
I see. So they're all in one piece.
What is it?
I'm fine.
Is it just me or is it just me?
The cicada I'm looking at... it looks CG to me.
Maybe it's not right.
I saw them this summer too, but they're CG.
No, no, no, this is it.
This is the real thing.
Over here is a waterfowl.
It's a bird.
You often see them in ponds, right? In the park.
Over...
You mean it has another name?
Yes, I do.
It's necessary.
Whenever I see this over, I think of how clear the face is.
It's like...
It's so black and white that it looks as if someone painted it.
Black, basically. The beak is white.
It's called an "over". You didn't know?
Well, well, well, well... we'll see about the creation of the creatures in the date shop.
If you have any more questions, please send them to us.
Thank you very much for watching.
So, for those of you who are watching the live broadcast... sorry to keep you waiting... but we have a few more announcements to make.
We've got a lot of announcements this time as well.
For example, we've just seen Auburn, and we did this again last year.
We handed out triangular raffle tickets again at the "Great Joy of the Devil" event, and if you won, you got a prize.
If you win, you get an original drawing.
Our masterpieces are on their way to you.
That's all well and good, but I'd like to commemorate something.
We've done a lot of great work, haven't we?
Last year, my sister drew them.
But this time, we were listening to each other's drawings, right?
You don't know who wrote it... maybe you should put it in the back.
Sure... "Sviiazhsak"...
I don't understand it. It's like a painting.
I see... so, let's say I get this large one...
Who is it? Who is it?
I'll write it on the back of the house.
Thank you, sir.
I'm writing too.
I wonder if there's a new European version of this.
like a large format Eiji...
Oh, yeah?
Is it important?
Let's go with something like that.
Cute!
Is it a signature?
Yes.
So cute.
It's so cute.
Cute
Eiji Ooban
Yo-ho!
It's good!
If you stand over like this, I've written it down for you.
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
Cute!
Over page
Yes, yes, yes...
So, by all means, everyone!
Even at a quick glance, you can't tell what it is.
I don't know...
Oh my God!
What is this? Is it a koala?
Oh, I think I got something back... honey...
Was it a bear?
Is it me?
Is that you?
Isn't this one too? This one that looks like a cow. Oh, is that me, too? Maybe. Oh, it's got some really bad stuff on it.
I don't know what it means. It's usually like that, isn't it? A little bit. Well, there are a lot of other rollers, anyway.
I hope everyone is looking forward to the day of the event, and by the way, thanks to the many people who have already purchased the items, there are many people who are interested in the event.
I'm sure there are some of you who have already bought a variety of items, but there is also a special gift for those who have purchased a Vip stone, which is a sacosh.
I'm sure there are some of you who have already purchased a variety of items, but I'm sure you'll be able to get a Sakosh, the Bip's designated stone, which is a very strong item.
This is a very cute one.
There are only a few BipCy Secure stores that give out these sakosh.
So please take this opportunity. We only have a few.
I don't know how many we have.
I don't think there are many left, but there could be a lot more than you think.
I'm sure there's probably very little left, but it's possible that there's a surprisingly large surplus.
I was standing by and waiting for the day's schedule, and then I was called in without really knowing what to do.
I was called out of the blue... to a place I didn't know.
Hey! I'm a little scared! Like, "Hey! I'm scared!
Like that? Like, "Hey, you're scaring me.
Hey, you're a little scary! I was called to do something I didn't understand.
I don't know what it was.
I don't know.
I'm sure Speecey saw me and did something bad to the kid.
I'm sure Speece saw the kid do something bad.
I don't have any children.
I'm sure Speece is watching you and he's done something wrong.
I'll make it longer.
I see.
I see...
I'm sure you've been here recently.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who are interested in VIP seats, right?
If you buy them, they'll be VIPs.
They let you in the back, where you sit, and it's so cool.
I heard a lot of celebrities come here. I've never been, but I've never been there at all.
I've heard that a lot of celebrities come to the Bubble Key, Bubble Key, yes, well, well, well, well...
So, I'm sorry, I'll be back next week at 8:00 p.m., 8:00 p.m., yes, that's right, last week we had a break in the live broadcast.
So it's been two weeks since we had a live broadcast.
Hey, I ate some really expensive food last week... I'm sorry, I shouldn't have said that.
I ate the most expensive food ever!
I was taking pictures of myself with my cell phone, and when they came out, I didn't know what they were, and I thought, "What is this? I was like, "Oh my God, did I eat this?
Then I looked at the time and I thought, "Oh my God, it looks so good!
If a gourmand were to see it, he would probably faint on the spot, because of the way it looked.
Oh, my gosh. By the way...
Oh, the picture.
Here it is.
Oh, no! Wait, wait, wait.
I'll tell you more about it.
I'll tell you more next week.
We'll know more next week when it airs.
Boober. The day before.
I'll eat anything if I can't fit it in the scale.